<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[Our technology experts search the planet for innovative products, and after a rigorous evaluation process, we select the best products. The result of our work is what you see here.]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[Our technology experts search the planet for innovative products, and after a rigorous evaluation process, we select the best products. The result of our work is what you see here.]]></description>
        <link>http://www.syftkogtech.com/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 05:11:52 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="http://www.syftkogtech.com/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 05:11:50 GMT</pubDate>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[News in brief: Linux advice for Equifax; fired
over phish; Security.txt standard proposed ]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/c2583c74-97a8-4483-93d1-39e9dc32878e.png">,<h1>News in brief: Linux advice for Equifax; fired
over phish; Security.txt standard proposed </h1>,<p>
Would
SeLinux have stopped Equifax Breach ?</p>,<p>
Writing
on the Double Pulsar site, infosec practitioner&nbsp;Kevin Beaumont
suggests&nbsp;Security
Enhanced Linux (SELinux) would have saved Equifax&nbsp;from
the&nbsp;disastrous
breach&nbsp;it
disclosed earlier this month.</p>,<p>
If you’re going to have Apache Struts facing the internet, SELinux is
the way to go, he wrote, referring to the&nbsp;Apache
Struts vulnerability the thieves exploited:</p>,<p>“ <em>This is the #1 thing almost every organisation seems to miss.&nbsp;Security
Enhanced Linux is</em><em>very
simple to deploy — usually just one command — and it
beefs up security on processes. Correctly deployed, it stops Tomcat
accessing the system — so stops unknown exploits.”</em></p>,<p><em>~</em>by<em></em>Bill Brenner</p>,<p>The
article goes on to describe how the absence of SELinux makes things
easy for the bad guys, and how IT/infosec practitioners can get the
best bang from it.</p>,<h2>BBC: Finance director phished, then fired</h2>,<p>The BBC has a cautionary tale for pretty much everyone who uses
email. It’s the story of a finance director who was sacked after
falling for a phishing scam disguised as a message from the boss. The
name of the company and the players are anonymous in the story, but
the BBC describes the sequence of events this way:</p>,<p>The email from
the boss looked kosher. He said a new supplier needed paying urgently
– £50,000 to secure an important contract. He wanted it done as
soon as possible because he was on holiday and didn’t want to worry
anymore about work. This rang true to the finance director because
his boss had already posted a photo of his Greek island getaway on
Instagram. His email address looked genuine too. But, of course, it
wasn’t the boss.</p>,<p>It was a fraudster who’d done his research and was
skilled at psychological manipulation. The small manufacturing firm –
that wishes to remain anonymous – ended up losing £150,000 to the
fraudster in the mistaken belief that he was a legitimate supplier.
When the boss found out the bad news, he fired the finance director.</p>,<p>The article says to beware of three words in any email subject
field: “urgent”, “payment” and “request”.</p>,<h2>
Proposed
Security.txt standard resembles Robots.txt</h2>,<p>Security researcher and web developer Ed Foudil has an idea he
hopes the Internet Engineering Task Force (IETF) will go for:
<a href="https://www.ietf.org/id/draft-foudil-securitytxt-00.txt">turning&nbsp;security.txt
into a standard</a>.&nbsp;security.txt is&nbsp;a file webmasters can
host on their domain root and use to describe the site’s security
policies. It’s a lot like&nbsp;robots.txt, a standard websites use
to communicate and define policies for web and search engine
crawlers.</p>,<p>The difference is that security.txt would be specific to security
policies.</p>,<p>In his paper,&nbsp;Foudil says the following:</p>,<p>When security risks in web services are discovered by
independent security researchers who understand the severity of the
risk, they often lack the channels to properly disclose them. As a
result, security issues may be left unreported. Security.txt defines
a standard to help organizations define the process for security
researchers to securely disclose security vulnerabilities.</p>,<p>According to Bleepingcomputer, it would <a href="https://www.bleepingcomputer.com/news/security/security-txt-standard-proposed-similar-to-robots-txt/">work
this way</a>:</p>,<ul><li>A security researcher finds a
	security vulnerability on a website 
	</li><li>He/she accesses the site’s security.txt file for
	information on how to contact the company and securely report the
	issue. 
	</li></ul>,<p>Security.txt is currently labelled as an “Internet Draft”, the
first IETF regulatory step in a three-stage process that also
includes&nbsp;<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Request_for_Comments">RFC
(Request For Comment)</a>&nbsp;and official&nbsp;<a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Internet_Standard">Internet
Standards</a>.</p>,<p><em><a href="https://nakedsecurity.sophos.com/2017/09/19/">Catch
up with all of today’s stories on Naked Security</a></em></p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.syftkogtech.com/news-in-brief-linux-advice-for-equifax-fired-over-phish-s/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">ae3690f2-a162-4e1a-a325-b2c42c69bcad</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 03:06:37 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[IRS Issues Ransomware Warning After Malicious Tax
Email is Distributed]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/1b339ee7-4d20-4513-86fa-06749d5905a3.jpg">,<h1>IRS Issues Ransomware Warning After Malicious Tax
Email is Distributed</h1>,<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/7d431aa7-ab87-47e4-a621-d9ec44cb0f6d.png">,<h4>IRS Releases a Ransomware Warning to All
Taxpayers</h4>,<p>The IRS has issued a new ransomware warning to all taxpayers.
&nbsp;Cyber criminals have begun sending out malicious email
campaigns with a “message” from the IRS and FBI. &nbsp;According
to the email, tax payers must download a questionnaire regarding
changes to the laws regarding tax compliance. &nbsp;However, it is no
questionnaire at all. &nbsp;Instead, the user downloads ransomware.
&nbsp;Below you will see an example of the malicious correspondence:</p>,<p>IRS Commissioner,&nbsp;&nbsp;John Koskinen, made the following
statement to <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/kellyphillipserb/2017/08/29/irs-issues-urgent-warning-about-ransomware-email-scam/#5104523861e3">Forbes</a>,</p>,<p>“People should stay vigilant against email scams that
try to impersonate the IRS and other agencies that try to lure you
into clicking a link or opening an attachment. &nbsp;People with a
tax issue won’t get their first contact from the IRS with a
threatening email or phone call.”</p>,<p>If you have already clicked to download the “questionnaire”,
do not pay the ransom demand. &nbsp;Paying the ransom is never a
guarantee you will get your data back, and it only reinforces the
criminal behavior. &nbsp;Instead, immediately report any ransomware
attempt or attack to the FBI at the Internet Crime Complaint
Center,&nbsp;<a href="http://www.ic3.gov/">www.IC3.gov</a>.
You should also forward any IRS-themed scams to&nbsp;phishing@irs.gov.</p>]]></description>
            <link>http://www.syftkogtech.com/irs-issues-ransomware-warning-after-malicious-tax-email-is-d/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">a5362a95-49c3-4fed-884d-87cdad22ad65</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 10:21:32 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Sarahah slurps up contacts 
]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="https://the-grid-user-content.s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/79d59d57-029b-4637-ac51-707fee00821a.jpg">,<iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2FWXDpCTrWdMQ%3Ffeature%3Doembed&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DWXDpCTrWdMQ&image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FWXDpCTrWdMQ%2Fhqdefault.jpg&key=a715cf41cc93453ca338d350cd26f87b&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=youtube" width="640" height="360" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>,<h1>Sarahah slurps up contacts 
</h1>,<p>Many social media apps sink their fangs into users’ devices to
suck out their contact lists.</p>,<p>It makes sense. How else would they a) offer to hook you up with
people you know and/or b) <a href="https://nakedsecurity.sophos.com/2015/10/05/linkedin-set-to-pay-13-million-compensation-over-its-email-persistence/">send
a swarm of marketing email</a>&nbsp;to pester your friends?</p>,<p>It’s not only potentially useful; it has the potential to drive
your buddies insane with the resulting plague of marketing email, if
<a href="https://nakedsecurity.sophos.com/2013/09/24/linkedin-denies-charges-that-it-hacks-users-email/">LinkedIn’s
past pestering</a> is any indication.</p>,<p>And now, there’s a problem with the way that the latest viral
sensation app, Sarahah, siphons contact lists. Namely, it is quietly
sucking up users’ contacts, but it’s not giving them anything in
return.</p>,<p>Sarahah, the <a href="https://nakedsecurity.sophos.com/2017/08/11/latest-viral-sensation-app-sarahah-raises-concerns-about-cyberbullying/">latest
people-rating app,</a> bills itself as a way to “receive honest
feedback” from friends and employees… anonymously. How the
“anonymous” part of the equation jibes with showing users who
else they know on the app is anybody’s guess.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://youtu.be/WXDpCTrWdMQ</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">556b0025-94ed-470e-9436-4b85bb2a66a5</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 21:14:57 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxNkTFvwjAQhff8CiuVIJHADqgUaBIGpA4sLG2nqqqMfYYEYke2E4qq_vdeIEjdfL5P7-69y2TRkkLmodqNrTE-XGUMv1ZB5oQtar-KVKOFL4yO5Ii4EbIx-QkIabklJdaqdCQnku7Bv5ygAu3d-vLG91teQeTij-QzRbpQJPrPrC8bGaFUTCz4xuqO6YWEBe6h51AhxQYtJPYKecOoswLLkDFhtAbhqeICdsYcqQbPQH-9vzInj7R0D99qV53yyaAF69BE3k7pJBnwut7IfDpNZrPFPHl8mi-my2XYqaMdWnOLo7dGAi20A-vXoIyFqLcbp8FvJI1ougVHZHgLaoiv-xrj0uH4YRynGetjDLIuaHHizl2zFqa6ZhUSyT0fHyyoPDx4Xz8zdj6fqbsofzR7D-JAkWU9p5uqNs6jxux-qT_cW5NE" height="244"></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJxNkTFvwjAQhff8CiuVIJHADqgUaBIGpA4sLG2nqqqMfYYEYke2E4qq_vdeIEjdfL5P7-69y2TRkkLmodqNrTE-XGUMv1ZB5oQtar-KVKOFL4yO5Ii4EbIx-QkIabklJdaqdCQnku7Bv5ygAu3d-vLG91teQeTij-QzRbpQJPrPrC8bGaFUTCz4xuqO6YWEBe6h51AhxQYtJPYKecOoswLLkDFhtAbhqeICdsYcqQbPQH-9vzInj7R0D99qV53yyaAF69BE3k7pJBnwut7IfDpNZrPFPHl8mi-my2XYqaMdWnOLo7dGAi20A-vXoIyFqLcbp8FvJI1ougVHZHgLaoiv-xrj0uH4YRynGetjDLIuaHHizl2zFqa6ZhUSyT0fHyyoPDx4Xz8zdj6fqbsofzR7D-JAkWU9p5uqNs6jxux-qT_cW5NE</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">09d2f97f-5020-4aad-a473-03510e6dae4d</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2017 02:26:28 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Stuxnet Anatomy of a Computer Virus]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2FnEsNnwZpXrk%3Ffeature%3Doembed&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DnEsNnwZpXrk&image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FnEsNnwZpXrk%2Fhqdefault.jpg&key=b7d04c9b404c499eba89ee7072e1c4f7&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=youtube" width="640" height="360" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>https://youtu.be/nEsNnwZpXrk</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">6436e1e7-fafd-44cb-8c98-8bc4e2a39e7a</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2017 20:48:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[How to Make Money as a Writer]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>How to Make Money as a Writer</h1><p>English Literature professor Dr Tyra Seldon teaches you how to make money as a writer</p><img src="https://www.filepicker.io/api/file/w8C0rat3RUeQ5Xet2Hta"></article>]]></description>
            <link>http://theblackbusinessschool.com/p/how-to-make-a-living-as-a-writer/?product_id=286092&amp;coupon_code=FIRSTMONTHFREE061017&amp;a_aid=57465b6d9f52d&amp;a_bid=5340dcb8</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">76faac66-1f60-434b-816c-fcc42c51e7c8</guid>
            <pubDate>Fri, 25 Aug 2017 18:04:35 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJw9j8sOgjAURH-FdG-LCT5jNSwk4COAJkZXBrmXtom1WKr8vm-XZzIzmZmoyhYavcaWnEjn6mbMGJiyocIYcUZaGs0qY3XDgCHrRmFS56stKHuo4nWWLcpdHo2yOh2mOpZpu1xfgwDzaJ50DkcXVGKfdDf7kN0Vtq-aGeoTAiBwZ29IvFaBk5wM-j7xJCohHSc9_wnvWSdjAS0nT9aFFerys_yFb94n05UpQF0EpXTCPqemD4gMSgk" height="500"></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJw9j8sOgjAURH-FdG-LCT5jNSwk4COAJkZXBrmXtom1WKr8vm-XZzIzmZmoyhYavcaWnEjn6mbMGJiyocIYcUZaGs0qY3XDgCHrRmFS56stKHuo4nWWLcpdHo2yOh2mOpZpu1xfgwDzaJ50DkcXVGKfdDf7kN0Vtq-aGeoTAiBwZ29IvFaBk5wM-j7xJCohHSc9_wnvWSdjAS0nT9aFFerys_yFb94n05UpQF0EpXTCPqemD4gMSgk</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1aee4ebf-df05-4d07-af92-b58e268af8bf</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 07:14:16 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[17101009 1218319511597872 4983430487461593088 n]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p><strong>The Surprising Way African-American Soldiers Were Recruited for World War I<br> Lily Rothman</strong></p>,<p>When the new PBS documentary series The Great War arrives this April to mark the 100-year anniversary of the U.S. entry into World War I on April 6, 1917, it will aim to tell the story of the American experience of the war, from the biggest moments to more obscure slices of history.<br> One of those slices is seen here, in the first exclusive clip released from the film, and it's a fitting reminder as Black History Month comes to a close of the obstacles faced and achievements recorded by African-Americans during that pivotal period of American history.<br> As the U.S. prepared to join in on a conflict that had previously been confined largely to the other side of the world, leaders within the African-American community in Harlem petitioned for the U.S. military to start a new regiment within the segregated armed forces so that black Americans could prove their strength and love of country just like their white fellow citizens could. The result was the African-American 15th National Guard — with the caveat that the unit had to raise its own money for equipment and serve under the command of a white officer.</p>,<p>Despite the conditions placed on the 15th National Guard (later re-designated the 369th Infantry Regiment, known as the "Harlem Hellfighters"), some of the biggest names around signed up, like bandleader James Reese Europe, who would help form the regimental band for the unit.<br> And, after the declaration of war came, the group saw record recruits — thanks in part to the unconventional recruiting technique is seen in this clip, using music to draw young men to the recruiting office.<br> Get your history fix in one place: sign up for the weekly TIME History newsletter<br> TIME revisited the story in 1941 when the coming of World War II made the military band newly relevant:<br> Bandmaster of the 369 th for more than four years has been Russell Wooding, onetime Broadway arranger, and conductor, onetime bandmaster for the New York Giants football team. Bandmaster Wooding works his men hard, says: "All of us realize that we have a great tradition to uphold." That tradition was begun in World War I, when the 369 th was the crack 15th New York Infantry and its bandmaster was the late James Reese Europe.<br> In the early 1900s, when Northern popular musicians played only potted-palm tunes, big, black, Alabama-born Jim Europe held Negro jam sessions in a cafe in West 53rd Street. White folks dropped in, hired so many of Europe's friends to play "gigs" — single party dates — that Jim opened a booking office. He formed a Clef Club of Negro jazzmen, gave a concert at Carnegie Hall in 1911. He (at the piano) and his boys played for Vernon and Irene Castle. Once he excited the Castles' curiosity by playing Memphis Blues too slow for their brisk one-step. That, said Jim Europe and his friends, was how the fox trot started.<br> In 1917 Jim Europe and his manager, Noble Sissle (Shuffle Along), joined the 15th Regiment. The colonel made Europe band leader, raised $10,000 for instruments — 30 reeds, a dozen or so brasses, two bull fiddles (for concerts). Leader Europe became a lieutenant, Sissle his drum major and top sergeant. The two of them were soon putting riffs in conventional marches, had the band blare blues to a fare-thee-well. When the 15th reached France, Europe's band was detailed to play for U. S. soldiers just back from the front lines.<br> The three-part series The Great War premieres on April 10.</p>,<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJwlzUsOwiAQANCrkDlA0di6MKUbd95Ad3wGIQFphiETb6_RC7y35ki2opIcOBlYzgdQCfMzsYHTcQHVyRtIzHu_aC0i07sNHg4n36rG6jDo-X7Fm8X4qDOoH-caBSQDX8yW0iSOUronxNe26v-4fQDBOymp" height="244"></iframe>,<p>The Surprising Way African-American Soldiers Were Recruited for World War I Lily Rothman When the new PBS documentary series The Great War arrives this April to mark the 100-year anniversary of the U.S. entry into World War I on April 6, 1917, it will aim to tell the story of the American experience of the war, from the biggest moments to more obscure slices of history.</p>,<p>by syftkog on YouTube</p>,<p><strong>Edit</strong></p>]]></description>
            <link>https://youtu.be/4YCeJaefZm4</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">140eeb9c-3f15-4338-8271-97ea6563297b</guid>
            <pubDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 07:34:44 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[No title]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<iframe src="https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJw9j8sOgjAURH-FdE8LUdEY0LjRGEkQNe6x99KWWKul2ujX-0KXZzIzmUlVbSuNQWt5RqRz53bMGBjeUmGMOCLlRrPaWN0yYMji-Wx5LvMtr9VFFHv76ONdVuvRCjahTJryGg-jPNo1zSwse7dCmtiHi8HKs5tC_66Zoj4gAELm7BVJ4BU4mZFhEpFAohLSdfCZdTAW0GbkxbqyQp1-lr_Q5SMyyU0F6iQopSn7npo8AbiFSlc" height="807"></iframe>]]></description>
            <link>https://the-grid.github.io/ed-userhtml/?g=eJw9j8sOgjAURH-FdE8LUdEY0LjRGEkQNe6x99KWWKul2ujX-0KXZzIzmUlVbSuNQWt5RqRz53bMGBjeUmGMOCLlRrPaWN0yYMji-Wx5LvMtr9VFFHv76ONdVuvRCjahTJryGg-jPNo1zSwse7dCmtiHi8HKs5tC_66Zoj4gAELm7BVJ4BU4mZFhEpFAohLSdfCZdTAW0GbkxbqyQp1-lr_Q5SMyyU0F6iQopSn7npo8AbiFSlc</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">1c92ea22-6124-4c08-9590-d89764264ae8</guid>
            <pubDate>Mon, 04 Sep 2017 08:58:42 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Why bashing Morgan Freeman, of all people, is
suddenly the rage in Russia]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<h1>Why bashing Morgan Freeman, of all people, is
suddenly the rage in Russia</h1>,<iframe src="https://cdn.embedly.com/widgets/media.html?src=https%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fembed%2FUz9PNoecNxU%3Ffeature%3Doembed&url=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.youtube.com%2Fwatch%3Fv%3DUz9PNoecNxU&image=https%3A%2F%2Fi.ytimg.com%2Fvi%2FUz9PNoecNxU%2Fhqdefault.jpg&key=a715cf41cc93453ca338d350cd26f87b&type=text%2Fhtml&schema=youtube" width="640" height="360" scrolling="no" frameborder="0" allowfullscreen></iframe>,<p>The 80-year-old
star’s tenure in the business probably failed to prep him for the
Russian reaction that greeted a two-minute online video he recorded
recently for a group hoping to keep alive concerns over Kremlin
meddling in the 2016 presidential election.</p>,<p>Freeman is being portrayed as a tool of the U.S. establishment
trying to bring down Trump, and as a man suffering from a “Messianic
complex” from movie roles playing God and the president of the
United States.</p>,<p>A “#StopMorganLie” hashtag is circulating aimed at
discrediting the actor.</p>,<p>In the controversial
video’s opening, Freeman dramatically declares: “We have been
attacked. We are at war.”</p>,<p>However the
Department Of Homeland Security have solid evidence regarding the
2016 election</p>,<p>“DHS notified the
Secretary of State or other chief election officer in each state of
any potential targeting we were aware of in their state leading up to
the 2016 election,” DHS spokesman Scott McConnell said. 
</p>,<p>The Department of
Homeland Security notified 21 states on Friday about attempts from
Russian governments hackers to breach their systems during the 2016
election. Among those that have confirmed that they were targeted are
Alabama, Washington, Wisconsin and Minnesota. Those four states said
that the breach attempts were unsuccessful. According to <em>Politico</em>,
a DHS official said that only a few networks were successfully
breached and none involved vote tallying. 
</p>,<p>In addition to
probing state election systems, U.S. officials say Russian hackers
are responsible for stealing and strategically leaking internal
documents from the Democratic Party and Hillary Clinton's campaign in
an effort to help elect President Donald Trump.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://youtu.be/Uz9PNoecNxU</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">aad1bca5-ee9a-4fd7-9a89-2e4dd5efd5d0</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 23 Sep 2017 05:11:50 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>